[
  {
    "headlines": [
      {
        "id": "4",
        "template_id": "3",
        "name": "The First Question",
        "sort_headline": "1",
        "creation_time": "2017-05-29 16:22:59",
        "question_position": "0",
        "questions": [
          {
            "id": "4",
            "headline_id": "4",
            "sort": "0",
            "question": "Select OS",
            "answer": "macOS",
            "keyword": "",
            "mandatory": "0",
            "question_type": "checkbox"
          },
          {
            "id": "5",
            "headline_id": "4",
            "sort": "4",
            "question": "Select Fruits",
            "answer": "Apples",
            "keyword": "",
            "mandatory": "1",
            "question_type": "checkbox"
          },
          {
            "id": "4",
            "headline_id": "4",
            "sort": "1",
            "question": "Select Language",
            "answer": "German",
            "keyword": "",
            "mandatory": "0",
            "question_type": "dropdown"
          },
          {
            "id": "4",
            "headline_id": "4",
            "sort": "2",
            "question": "Done?",
            "answer": "Yes!",
            "keyword": null,
            "mandatory": "1",
            "question_type": "radiobutton"
          },
          {
            "id": "4",
            "headline_id": "4",
            "sort": "3",
            "question": "textbox?",
            "input_type": "text",
            "keyword": null,
            "min_value": "0",
            "max_value": "100",
            "decimals": "2",
            "date_time_format": "MM:HH",
            "operator": "<",
            "variable": "$datetime$",
            "mandatory": "0",
            "question_type": "textbox"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "id": "5",
        "template_id": "3",
        "name": "A Second Question",
        "sort_headline": "2",
        "creation_time": "2017-05-29 21:29:59",
        "question_position": "0",
        "questions": [
          {
            "id": "14",
            "headline_id": "5",
            "sort": "0",
            "question": "Select Toppings",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "keyword": "",
            "mandatory": "0",
            "question_type": "checkbox"
          },
          {
            "id": "15",
            "headline_id": "5",
            "sort": "4",
            "question": "Choose colors!",
            "answer": "Teal",
            "keyword": "",
            "mandatory": "1",
            "question_type": "checkbox"
          },
          {
            "id": "14",
            "headline_id": "5",
            "sort": "1",
            "question": "Select Car!",
            "answer": "Bugatti",
            "keyword": "",
            "mandatory": "0",
            "question_type": "dropdown"
          },
          {
            "id": "4",
            "headline_id": "5",
            "sort": "2",
            "question": "Listen Radio?",
            "answer": "Yeah",
            "keyword": "tech",
            "mandatory": "1",
            "question_type": "radiobutton"
          },
          {
            "id": "14",
            "headline_id": "5",
            "sort": "3",
            "question": "Enter Text",
            "input_type": "text",
            "keyword": null,
            "min_value": "",
            "max_value": "",
            "decimals": "",
            "date_time_format": "MM:HH",
            "operator": "",
            "variable": "$datetime$",
            "mandatory": "0",
            "question_type": "textbox"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
]